
  [
    {
      "question": "What is the correct way to declare a variable in JavaScript?",
      "choice1": "var myVariable;",
      "choice2": "variable myVariable;",
      "choice3": " let myVariable;",
      "choice4": "const myVariable;",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question":
      "Which keyword is used to define a function in JavaScript?" ,
      "choice1":  "method",
      "choice2":  " function",
      "choice3":  " def" ,
      "choice4":  "func" ,  
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question":"How do you check the type of a variable in JavaScript?" ,
      "choice1": "typeof myVariable;",
      "choice2":" typeOf(myVariable);",
      "choice3": "checkType(myVariable);",
      "choice4": "myVariable.getType();",
      "answer": 1
    } ,
    {
      "question": "Which operator is used for equality comparison in JavaScript?" ,
      "choice1": "==",
      "choice2":  "=" ,
      "choice3":  " ===",
      "choice4":  "=>",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question":"What is the correct way to write a single-line comment in JavaScript?" ,
      "choice1": " // This is a comment" ,
      "choice2": "  <!-- This is a comment -->",
      "choice3": " /* This is a comment */" ,
      "choice4":  " # This is a comment" ,
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you add an element to the end of an array in JavaScript?" ,
      "choice1":  "array.push(element);" ,
      "choice2":  "array.add(element);",
      "choice3": "array.insert(element);",
      "choice4":  "array.append(element);",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the NaN value represent in JavaScript?" ,
      "choice1": "Negative number",
      "choice2": " Not a Number",
      "choice3": "Null value",
      "choice4": "Negative infinity",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which method is used to remove the last element from an array in JavaScript?" ,
      "choice1": "array.removeLast();",
      "choice2": " array.pop();",
      "choice3": " array.deleteLast();",
      "choice4":  " array.splice(-1);",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you convert a string to an integer in JavaScript?" ,
      "choice1":  " parseString()",
      "choice2": " convertToInt()",
      "choice3":  "  parseInt()",
      "choice4":  " stringToInteger()",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which method is used to select an HTML element by its ID in JavaScript?" ,
      "choice1":  " selectElementById()",
      "choice2": " getElementByID()",
      "choice3":  " getID()" ,
      "choice4": "document.getElementById()",
      "answer": 4
    }
  ]